welltern.com 2018-05-12

# W&T Zippers of the Highest Quality

Thank you for visiting www.welltern.com. Welltern. is committed to protect your privacy. We will not collect your personal information when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

## Information Collected

If you browse our website or download information, we will automatically store the following information about your visit:

  * The page(s) you visit
  * The date and time you accessed our website
  * The type of operating system used to access our website
  * The type of browser used to access our website
  * The Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our website
  * The search term(s) used in your search engine

We gather this information to learn about the number of visitors to our website. This helps use make our website more user friendly. We do not record information about individuals and their visits, and will not identify you personally.

## Sending Us Personal Information

If you submit your personal information via e-mail, sign-up, or filling out a form through our website, we use that information to respond to your message, to fulfill your request, or provide you with information. Welltern will not share, release, publish, disclose, rent, or sell any personally identifiable information to any third parties.

## Your Rights

You have the right to request to modify or to be removed from our active e-mail database list. To request changes, send an e-mail to [info@welltern.com](mailto:info@welltern.com "Email Our Company") asking to update certain personally identifiable information, or to be removed from our active e-mail list.

We will comply with your request as soon as reasonably possible. To protect your confidentiality, we can only send the request to the e-mail address listed in our database. We do maintain back-up copies of your personally identifiable information and reserve the right to contact former users of the website from time to time.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Because of changing technology and marketing demands, we reserve the right to change our policies regarding privacy of your personally identifiable information in the future. If that happens, we will promptly update this Privacy Policy. We may also attempt to provide a message to our customers whose e-mail addresses we have, in conformity with this Privacy Policy, advising of any change(s).

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@welltern.com](mailto:info@welltern.com "Email Our Company").
